### **LUCY ADWOA QUAYSON**

Accra, Ghana quaysonlucyofficial@gmail.com +233 26 139 1449

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am skilled and experience in using creative, technological and administrative knowledge to provide solutions to companies. My 6years of experience covers Office Administration, Graphic Design, Digital Marketing, Photography, Creative Writing and Video Editing among others.

My goal in career is using advanced technology coupled with creative and administrative skills to aid in executing the visions and missions of any country, institution, company, or personality. It is with this passion that I continue to improve my knowledge and skill in technology.

I am currently learning Software Engineering. I have used my Graphic Design skills to shoot ups the sales in previous institutions I have worked with, including, CompuGhana and Adansi Travels. My Digital marketing skills pushed the sales of Adansi Travels by 45% increase from 2021-2022.

I increased their presence on social media platforms and sold their product as and services to old and potential clients by creating the appropriate graphics and videos that attracts, scripting captions that captivates and using my analytical skills that targets the right clients. I increased their followers on Instagram from 7K to 11K under 4months.

Why is working with me any different from anyone else? Working with me is a great benefit to you because I never remain in the same level of knowledge and skill you employed me with. I constantly add up to my skill in ways that will be of great benefit to any organization I'm associated with.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **Creative & Production Manager**

# Adansi Travels | August 2020 (Present)

- Communicated with C.E.O and team marketing team on daily bases to translate all visions and solutions through visual design.
- Developed graphics and layouts for custom product illustrations, company logos and Internet websites.
- Designed stylish presentations that best communicated company services to clients.
- Edited raw videos brought in by trained tour leaders rom all travels.
- Communicated with various printing press to organize all company print outs including brochures, flyers, shirts, billboards etc.
- Supported the development, planning and implementation of communications strategies.
- Creating content and managing all social media platforms.
- Instagram Followers increased from (August 2020) 7.6K to 20,032 by August 2021 Facebook likes increased from (August 2020) 143K to 239.9 by August 2021
- Enhanced, retouched and resized photographs with Lightroom and Photoshop.

### Creative Director

# CompuGhana | August 2019 - August 2020

- Designed & created marketing & e-marketing materials on a range of projects.
- Prepared designs for printing by marking up layouts and writing final instructions.
- Supervised other Graphic Designers on how to complete a task and serving as communication link between Marketing Head and Designers.
- Managed the social media platforms (Instagram, Facebook, Twitter) of CompuGhana by analyzing the market and creating contents that best fits marketing ideas.
- Kept up to date with new software, post-production techniques & industry trends.
- Served as the company photographer to take pics for company artworks for marketing needs.
- Raised social media awareness hugely in the span of 9months.
- These were the increments they experienced: Instagram Follower increased from 15.6K to 26,321 by July 2020 || Facebook likes increased from 127K to 423,678 by July 2020 || Twitter Followers increased from 418 to 637 by July 2020.
- I also designed over 2,000 artworks for social media platforms and other company use.

# Co-Founder and Operations Lead

# Manifold Expressions | January 2015 - November 2018

- Handled all Marketing and Communications of various contracted agencies.
- Prepared presentations and proposals to prospective clients
- Attending corporate meetings and programs of clients to accumulate graphic and written contents for the social media managements of clients
- Dealt with complaints from agencies.
- Monitored, analyze and track online and client complains and providing the best solutions reduces general customer complains.

# I.T ASSISTANT

## Charisword Gospel Ministry | January 2016

- Assisting in the management of the whole I.T team which includes photographers, social media persons, sound engineers and graphics designer to provide excellent work.
- Taking, editing and submitting almost 400 photos every week.
- Holding consistent training to build new team members that joined the I.T Department.
- Communicate with I.T team to plan and create content by combining writing, photography, videography and graphic design skills to tell impactful stories about the organization.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems
- Supervising the designing of at least 3 artworks every week and editing audio messages of
- Used Microsoft Word and other software tools to create documents and other communications
- Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting.

## **SKILLS**

# **Professional**

- Excellent software proficiency (MS Office, Adobe Premier Pro, Illustrator, Photoshop, Lightroom).
- Typography, color and layout skills.
- Presentation Planning
- Company Logos
- Problem-Solving
- Advanced problem solving
- Strategic planning
- Excellent spoken and written english
- Verbal and Written Communication
- Teamwork
- Compassion
- Creative Thinking

## **LANGUAGES**

- English (Advanced Spoken and Written)
- Asante Twi (local)

## **EDUCATION**

# First Degree:

Course: Software Engineering Institution: Moringa School

Duration: March 2022 - October 2022

# First Degree:

Course: Political Science and Information Studies.

Institution: University of Ghana (Legon). Duration: November 2012 – July 2016.

## **CERTIFICATES**

## **Certificate of Completion:**

Course: Understanding the Impact of Deepfake Videos

Institution: LinkedIn Learning
Date Completed: July 23<sup>rd</sup>, 2022

Course: Artificial Intelligence Foundations: Machine Learning

Institution: LinkedIn Learning
Date Completed: July 25<sup>th</sup>, 2022

Course: Machine Learning with Python: Foundations

Institution: LinkedIn Learning
Date Completed: July 26<sup>th</sup>, 2022

Course: Teamwork

Institution: LinkedIn Learning
Date Completed: May 05<sup>th</sup>, 2022

Course: Leading Yourelf Institution: LinkedIn Learning Date Completed: May 05<sup>th</sup>, 2022

# Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

https://www.behance.net/lucyquayson www.linkedin.com/in/lucy-quayson

# REFERENCE Mr. Gills Michel C.E.O Great Graphics Africa Accra, Ghana +233 27 355 3553 gillsmichel@gmail.com

# Mr. Amewor Daniel

Co-Founder Manifold Expressions
Accra, Ghana
+233 20 588 2141 | ddkamewor@gmail.com